Hello I'm Tyhiesha Johnson

71 BIETOU RD, EASTRIDGE CAPE TOWN, 7785 (076) 077-5241 JOHNSONTYHIESHA@GMAIL.COM



Personal Information

Surname: Johnson

Full Name(s): TyhieshaJulia

Date of Birth: 29th September 1999

Nationality: South African

Language(s): English and Afrikaans

Gender: Female

Marital Status: Single

State of Health: Well

Driver's License: Learner's License

Skills

Native English speaker with a Neutral accent, organizational skills, developing lesson and education plans, clear communication, flawless pronunciation, time management, knowledge of literature, problem-solving, patience, MS Office skills and online savvy; Zoom, Google Meets and Teams, etc. I pay attention to detail and enjoy data analysis, I am a team player and have experience in overseeing mini projects and creating new ways to

Experience

April 2024

LC Studio - Cyber Security Intern (Full-time)

- Understanding cybersecurity fundamentals; security principles, risk management, etc.
- Developing practical skills; security tools, network security, operation system security, etc.

May 2023 - Present(Remote)

National Centre for Child Protection - Student Counsellor (Part-time)

- Crisis intervention for family/personal crisis.
- Emotional support and Case management for those with depression, anxiety, domestic abuse, etc.

February 2023 - February 2023 (Remote)

InfluenZArt - Social Media Manager

- Overseeing the organization's interactions with the public.
- Creating a strategy to gain more views in order to sell tickets.
- Copy writing new content with supplied footage.
- Editing and publishing engaging content daily.

March 2022 - June 2023 (Remote & On-site)

Georgen Creative - Social Media Manager and Brand Strategist (Part-time)

- Overseeing the organization's interactions with the public.
- Creating a strategy to gain more views in order to sell tickets.
- Copy writing new content with supplied footage.
- Editing and publishing engaging content daily.

January 2022 - March 2022 (Remote)

Private Tutor, Online and 1:1 - English, Afrikaans and Mathematics (Part-time)

- Tutored two adults in English Literature and Afrikaans FAL.
- Tutored two eighth grade students in Mathematics.
- Created lessons appropriate to government requirements in preparation for examinations.

November 2020 - December 2020 (On-site)

American Swiss, Tygervalley - Retail Sales Assistant (Seasonal)

- Identifying and providing the best possible solutions for customers.
- Assisting with replenishing of stock and visual merchandising.
- Brand ambassador.

March 2018 - February 2020 (On-site)

Georgen O ce (Pty) Ltd, Randburg - Assistant

Organizing and storing paperwork.

• Product finishing and packaging.

Education

DECEMBER 2023

University of the Western Cape, Cape Town - Bachelors of Arts Degree

Triple Majored in Psychology, English and Anthropology

NOVEMBER 2017

Harold Cressy High School, Cape Town - *Matriculant*

Subjects; English, Afrikaans, Life Science, Mathematical Literacy, History & Life Orientation

Certificates

APRIL 2024

Life Choices Academy, Cape Town - Full Stack Developer

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MySQL, Node.js & Vue.js

FEBRUARY 2022

Global Language Training, Online - TEFL Certificate (250hrs)

Certificate Number: GLT2022032288

- TeachingtheEnglishLanguageSkills
- PlanningLessons
- ManagingaClassroom
- SimplifyingEnglishGrammar